[Okita's sister, Mitsuba, falls ill right before her marriage to Kuraba.]
[Okita only wishes for his sister's remaining days to be happy, but the cold-hearted Hijikata will have none of that.]
[Oedo Hospital]
(ﾐﾂﾊﾞ)銀さん… 昨日は 山崎さんと
何を話していたんですか？
Gin-san...
What were you and Yamazaki-san talking about yesterday?
(銀時)あぁ？ 何でもねえよ
気にすんな｡
Huh? Nothing. Don't worry about it.
(ﾐﾂﾊﾞ)そう言われると
よけいに気になります｡
If you put it like that, it makes me worry even more.
野暮なこと聞くねぇ…｡
男が隠れて ｺｿｺｿ話してたら➡
Come on, don't ask silly questions.
When men get together and talk secretly about something...
これが 話題に決まってるだろ？
ｱﾝﾀも見る？
...then it's gotta be about this. You wanna see it?
[The Nurse's Fluttering Flowers.]
(ﾐﾂﾊﾞ)もう！
Oh my!
男の子って いくつになっても
そうなのね｡
I guess boys will always be boys.
集まっては つるんで
悪だくみばかりして…｡
They'll get together and be up to no good.
(かけ声)
(ﾐﾂﾊﾞ)あの人たちも そう…｡
Just like them...
That's all for today.
男同士でいるときが
いちばん楽しそうで…｡
They look the happiest when they're with other guys.
結局 女の子の入り込む
余地なんてないの｡
There really was no room for girls.
(はしゃぐ声)
And then they left without me.
(ﾐﾂﾊﾞ)みんな 私を
置いていってしまったわ｡
振り向きもしないで…｡
They didn't even look back.
こんないい女をほっといて
行っちまうなんざ…➡
What a bunch of terrible guys to have left such a good woman behind.
ひどい連中だねぇ｡
え？
そうでしょう… だから私
目一杯幸せになって➡
I know. That's why I'm going to become super happy and put them all to shame!
あの人たちを見返してあげるの｡
こんな歳まで 一人で
体のことでも➡
Being single up to this age and my poor health have caused So-chan a lot of worry.
総ちゃんには
心配かけてしまったもの｡
幸せになって 総ちゃんを
安心させてあげなきゃ｡
I have to find happiness so So-chan will no longer have to worry about me.
幸せにならなきゃね｡
Yes, I have to become happy.
Tenkaiya, the family Mitsuba will marry into...
((山崎:ﾐﾂﾊﾞ殿の 嫁ぎ先の転海屋
攘夷浪士と黒いつながりが…))
has some shady connections with the Anti-Foreigner Faction.
(咳)
おい 大丈夫か？
もう休んだほうが…｡
Hey, you okay? You should get some rest.
(咳)
体にさわるぞ！
You're putting stress on your body.
大丈夫… です｡
もうちょっと 誰かと➡
I'm...okay...
I just want to talk with someone for a little bit...
お話していたいの…｡
...more...
(咳)
Hey!
おい!?
(山崎)急に 容態が悪化したって…
かなり ﾏｽﾞｲみたいで…｡
Her condition suddenly turned worse.
It's not looking good.
(山崎)家族の者は それ相応の
覚悟をしておけと 医者が…｡
Her family should prepare for the worst.
That's what the doctor said.
Vice-Chief, please go to her.
(山崎)
副長 行ってあげてください｡
(山崎)こんなときに仕事なんざ…｡
How can you work at a time like this?
それも よりによって
ﾐﾂﾊﾞさんの婚約者を➡
And not only that, you're going to arrest Mitsuba's fiancé of all people...
しょっぴこうなんて…｡
That's cruel...too cruel.
酷です… あまりにも｡
ﾐﾂﾊﾞさんや 沖田隊長の気持も
考えてやってください｡
Please think of Mitsuba and Captain Okita's feelings.
副長が 間違ったことを
してるなんて思っちゃいませんよ｡
I don't think you're doing the wrong thing.
ﾔﾂらをほっときゃ いずれ
その武器で ｵﾚたちの仲間が➡
If we leave them be, then eventually their weapons may kill one of our own.
やられちまうかもしれない｡
でも 今やるべきことは
こんなことじゃないでしょう？
But what should be done right now...isn't this.
土方さん ｱﾝﾀのいるべき場所は
ここじゃないでしょ？
Hijikata-san, this is not where you should be right now.
Humph.
(土方)ﾌﾝ… ｵﾚが
薄情だとでも言うつもりか？
Are you trying to say I'm cold and heartless?
そうでもねえだろ｡
I don't think so.
ﾃﾒｴの嫁さんが
死にかけてるってのに➡
His wife is dying and yet the husband's out here trying to cut a deal.
こんなところで
商売にいそしんでる➡
旦那も いるってんだからよ｡
Hijikata-san.
土方さん？
(土方)山崎！ ｵﾒｴ➡
Yamazaki, you haven't told anyone else about this, have you?
この件 誰にも
他言しちゃいねえな？
は… はい｡
N-No...
知ってんのは 隊の中じゃ➡
So you and I are the only ones in the organization who know of this, right?
ｵﾚとお前だけだな？
はい…｡
Yes.
(土方)じゃ 引き続き この件は
極秘扱いってことで頼むぜ｡
In that case, I want you to keep this matter confidential, okay?
あ… 副長 ｱﾝﾀ… まさか！
Vice-Chief! You're not thinking of...!
副長～っ!!
Vice-Chief!!
(近藤)総悟！
いいかげん お前も休め！
Sogo!
You should get some rest.
昨日から
一睡もしてねえじゃねえか｡
You haven't slept a wink since yesterday.
ｵﾚと交代！ 寝てきたから ｵﾚ…｡
(沖田)ｸﾏ…｡
I'll switch with you. I've already slept.
Those dark circles.
ﾒｲｸだ これは…｡
(いびき)
It's just makeup.
Huh?
いいな ｱｲﾂは…｡
(いびき)
ﾉｰ天気で…｡
Man, it must be nice to be carefree like that.
つうか なんでいるの？
(いびき)
What's he doing here anyway?
ﾄｼと 派手にやりやったらしいな？
I heard you had a huge fight with Toshi.
珍しいじゃねえか｡
お前が負けるなんて…｡
It's not like you to lose.
今は 野郎の話は
やめてくだせぇ｡
Please don't talk about that bastard right now.
詳しくは
教えてくれんかったがな…➡
He didn't go into detail, but this is what he told me.
言ってたぞ 今のお前には
負ける気がせんと…｡
He said he feels like he would never lose to you right now.
I asked you not to talk about him!
(沖田)やめろって
言ってるんでえ!!
…何だってんだ｡
どいつもこいつも➡
What's the deal? Why does everyone talk about Toshi all the time?
二言目には ﾄｼﾄｼって…｡
肝心の野郎は どうしたい？
So where the hell is that bastard right now?
姉上が こんなだってのに
姿も見せねえ…｡
My sister's like this yet he won't even show his face.
昔 ふった女が死のうが
知ったこっちゃねえってかい？
So he doesn't give a damn if a woman he dumped is dying?
さすがに ﾓﾃる男は違うときた｡
Well I guess that's how it is when you're popular with the girls, huh?
やっぱり お前
疲れてるみてえだな… 寝ろ｡
Looks like you are tired after all. You should get some rest.
軽蔑しましたか？
Do you despise me now?
…寝ろ！
ｼﾞｬﾏですかい？ ｵﾚは…｡
Go rest.
Am I just a nuisance?
土方さんと違って…｡
Unlike Hijikata-san...
Chief!!
(山崎)局長～！ 大変なんです～！
This is terrible!!
副長がぁぁ!!
The Vice-Chief is...!!
Hm?
転海屋 蔵場 当馬だな｡
You're Toma Kuraba of Tenkaiya, right?
御用改めである
神妙にしてもらおうか｡
The jig is up.
Cooperate and this will go easier for you.
(蔵場)あなたは いつぞやの…｡
You're that guy from before...
武器密輸 及び 不逞浪士との
違法取引の容疑で➡
You are under arrest on charges of smuggling weapons and illegal dealings with ronin.
お前を逮捕する…
神妙に お縄につけ｡
Come with me quietly.
ﾌﾌｯ… 友人の婚約者を
ためらいなく捕まえますか｡
So you can arrest your friend's fiancé without any hesitation?
なかなか 太い神経を
おもちのようで…｡
You've got a lot of nerve.
犯罪に手え染めながら
真選組の縁者に手え出すたあ➡
Getting involved with a relative of the Shinsengumi while dirtying your hands in a crime like this...
ｸｸｯ… ﾃﾒｴも 太え野郎じゃねえか｡
You've got a lot of nerve.
Toshi went by himself?
(近藤)ﾄｼが一人で!? 山崎！
Yamazaki! Why didn't you say anything?
ﾃﾒｴ なんで 今まで黙ってた！
すみません！ 副長に
固く口止めされていたんです！
I'm sorry!
But the Vice-Chief swore me to secrecy.
親類縁者に 攘夷浪士と
関係のある者がいることが➡
If the members found out that Captain Okita's relative is connected to Anti-Foreigner Faction samurai,
隊内に知れれば 沖田隊長が
真選組での立場を失うと…！
then the captain would lose his position in the Shinsengumi.
ﾄｼの野郎… ﾊﾅから ﾃﾒｴ一人で➡
Damn Toshi! He planned on doing this by himself from the start.
ｶﾀつけるつもりだったな…
ﾑﾁｬなﾏﾈを！
How reckless of him.
...Why...
《沖田:なんで…》
Whatever. What you do is up to you.
((知ったこっちゃねえんだよ…
お前のことなんざ))
That bastard!
あの野郎…！
お前は動くな｡
Don't you dare go anywhere.
(近藤)ﾐﾂﾊﾞ殿のそばにいてやれ｡
Stay by Mitsuba-dono.
それに… 今のお前では
足手まといだ｡
Besides...
...right now, you'll just get in the way.
剣に迷いのあるﾔﾂは死ぬ｡
Those who hesitate with their sword will die.
ｵﾚたちを信じろ ってかい…｡
So you want me to trust you?
冗談じゃねえ… ｵﾚは
野郎に貸しを作るのだきゃあ➡
You've gotta be kidding me.
There's no way I'm gonna be indebted to that bastard.
ご免こうむるぜ！
Kondo-san... You have the wrong idea about me.
近藤さん… ｱﾝﾀはｵﾚを誤解してる｡
ｵﾚは ｱﾝﾀが思うほど
きれいじゃねえ｡
I'm not as pure as you think I am.
(沖田)人を信じるとか
そういうﾔﾂじゃねえんだ｡
I'm not one to trust others.
ﾃﾒｴのことしか考えちゃいねえ｡
I only think of myself.
Even when we were together, I always felt a gap between us.
いつも ｱﾝﾀたちと一緒にいても
溝を感じてた｡
ｵﾚは ｱﾝﾀらとは違うって…｡
I always felt I was different from you guys.
That's why, my sister, you and him...
だから 姉上もｱﾝﾀも ｱｲﾂの…｡
Chief!
局長！
ってえ… ずいぶんと
ｵﾚには手厳しいな 近藤さんは｡
Boy, you really are harsh on me, aren't you, Kondo-san?
そりゃ お前がｶﾞｷだからだ｡
That's because you're a kid.
ﾄｼがお前と同じこと言ったら
ｵﾚは ﾔﾂも殴ったよ｡
If Toshi said the same thing as you, I would've hit him too.
ｵﾚたちは そういう仲だろ？
Isn't that how our relationship is?
(近藤)誰かがねじ曲がれば➡
If one of us strayed, then the other two will punch him back to where he belongs.
他の２人が ぶん殴って
まっすぐに戻す｡
昔からそうだった…｡
It's always been like that.
だから ｵﾚたちは
永遠に曲がらねえ！
That's why we'll never stray. We'll always live a straight life.
ずっと まっすぐ生きていける｡
ﾃﾒｴが勝手に掘った
小せえ溝なんて➡
We don't know anything about this small gap that you claim to have built.
ｵﾚたちゃ知らねえよ そんなもん！
But I'll keep jumping over that and punching you out as many times as I can.
何度でも飛び越えてって➡
何度でも ﾃﾒｴを
ぶん殴りにいってやる！
そんな連中 長え人生でも➡
Friends like that are hard to find in this life.
そうそう会えるもんじゃ
ねえんだよ｡
We're really lucky, you know.
ｵﾚたちは 幸せ者だぜ｡
To have found two bad friends like that in our lives.
そんな悪友を 人生で
２人も得たんだ｡
総悟… もし ｵﾚが
曲がっちまったときは➡
Sogo...
If I ever go astray, it will be your turn to punch me, all right?
今度は お前がｵﾚを
殴ってくれよな｡
She loved him...
(沖田)惚れてたんですよ…➡
本気で｡
With all her might...
Even after being treated so coldly by him, she still waited for him to come home.
冷たく突っぱねられながら➡
それでも ずっと
野郎の帰りを待ってた…｡
ずっと…｡
She always did.
(雄叫び)
She finally got over him and was about to be happy when...
(沖田)ようやく吹っ切って
幸せ つかみかけたと思ったら➡
また ｱｲﾂだ…｡
...he appeared again.
How many times will he stand in the way of my sister's happiness?
何度 姉上のｼﾞｬﾏをしやがる｡
ひでえﾔﾂだ…｡
What an asshole.
ひでえﾔﾂだよ ﾎﾝﾄ…｡
He's an asshole. He really is...
わかってまさあ… ｵﾚの姉上が➡
But I know... I know that my sister would never fall in love with an asshole.
ひでえﾔﾂに惚れるわきゃ
ねえってことくらい｡
ﾎﾝﾄは わかってた…｡
In all honesty, I understood.
いつ死ぬともしれねえ身で➡
I understood that a guy who always faced death couldn't risk taking care of my sister.
野郎が 姉上を受け入れる
わきゃねえってことくらい…｡
わかってた…｡
I understood...that he turned her down because he thought that would be better for my sister.
野郎が 姉上の幸せを思って
拒絶してたことくらい｡
わかってた…｡
I understood...that all he really wanted was for my sister to be happy.
野郎も 姉上の幸せを
願ってることくらい…｡
わかってたんですよ ｵﾚは…｡
I understood all of this... But it still gets on my nerves.
でも しゃくじゃないですか｡
野郎は 気にくわねえ｡
He pisses me off.
気にくわねえ野郎のままで
いいんでい…｡
And that's fine with me.
よいしょっと…｡
All right then...
旦那 長え話 聞いてくれて
ありがとうございやした｡
Boss, thanks for listening to my long story.
ｺｲﾂは 姉上には内緒で…
って 聞いてるわきゃねえか｡
Don't tell my sister this, okay?
Oh, never mind, it's not like you were listening anyway.
He took away a lot of important things from me, but I still gotta go.
野郎には 大事なもん
いろいろ持っていかれたが➡
行かなきゃならねえ…｡
近藤さんには
死ぬと言われたんでねえ…｡
Kondo-san told me I'd die.
最後かもしれねえ｡
So this may be the last time.
地蔵にでも 全部
しゃべっときたかったのさ｡
I just needed to get it all off my chest to someone, even if it's to a Jizo statue.
[Note: Jizo statues are part of the Buddhist religion and said to be guardians of dead children.]
その大事なもんに…｡
One of the important things you talked about...
ｱｲﾂも入っちまってんだろ？
...includes him, right?
(沖田)旦那…｡
Boss.
(あくび)
よく寝たぜ…｡
That was a good nap.
I'll go with you so I can shake off this grogginess.
さて 眠気覚ましに
いっちょ いくか…｡
ﾃﾒｴの姉ちゃんにも 友達だって
ｳｿ ぶっこいちゃったし｡
After all, I lied to your sister about how we were friends and all.
最後まで付き合うぜ… 総一郎君｡
I'll be with you till the end, Soichiro-kun.
旦那… ｸﾏ｡
Boss...those black circles...
ﾁﾝﾋﾟﾗに殴られた｡
Some punks beat me up.
Sister, I'm a lucky guy.
《沖田:姉上… ｵﾚは幸せ者だ｡
長え人生でも
そうそう会えるもんじゃねえ｡
You don't often meet friends like these in your lifetime.
そんな悪友を
人生で３人も得たんだ》
Yet, I already have three of these bad friends in my life.
うぉっ！
うぅっ!!
うおぉぉ～！
♪♪～
(黒幕)話が違うではないか！
蔵場殿｡
This is not what you told me, Kuraba-dono.
(黒幕)幕府の犬は すでに
抱き込んだと聞いていたが➡
I thought the Bakufu's dogs were already on our side.
あれなるは 真選組でも
鬼の副長と恐れられる➡
But that's Toshiro Hijikata of the Shinsengumi, feared by all as the demon Vice-Chief.
土方 十四郎｡
あれに嗅ぎつけられたのでは
卿も我らも ただではすむまい｡
If he's on our trail, then it'll be trouble for you and for us.
じき 加勢も来よう…｡
I'm sure reinforcements will be arriving soon.
(蔵場)いえ…
加勢が来るには遅すぎます｡
No.
It's already too late for reinforcements.
おそらく あの方 本当に一人で…｡
It looks like he really came here by himself.
一人で 何故？
By himself? Why?
(蔵場)さぁ… お侍様の考えは➡
Who knows? It's difficult for us merchants to understand how a samurai thinks.
私たち商人には
理解しかねますゆえ…｡
(黒幕)とすれば…｡
If that's the case...
あっ… うぅっ！
♪♪～
(黒幕)あれ一人を片づければ
事はすむわけだな…｡
All we have to do is take care of him and we'll be done.
(蔵場)あの方には
消えてもらいましょうか｡
Let's make sure he disappears, okay?
(助手)先生！
心拍 弱ってきています｡
Doctor!
Her pulse is getting weaker. Her life is in danger.
危険な状態です｡
(医師)手は尽くしたが もはや…｡
We did everything we could...but...
(医師)家族の方は？
Is her family here?
(看護師)あっ それが…｡
Well, the thing is...
♪♪～
《沖田:姉上 ごめんなさい…｡
Sister...
I'm sorry.
ｵﾚは… ｵﾚは…！》
I...
(ｻｲﾚﾝ)
(山崎)どけ～！
真選組のお通りだ～!!
Outta the way! Make way for the Shinsengumi!
《近藤:ﾄｼ… あのﾊﾞｶ野郎めが…｡
Toshi... That idiot...
総悟を隊から追い出そうなんてﾔﾂ
ｵﾚたちの中にいるかよ！
Who among us would ever want to kick Sogo out of the organization?
仲間だろうが！ ﾊﾞｶ野郎!!
We're all comrades, aren't we?
You idiot!
何でも一人で
しょい込みやがって…｡
Why do you always put all the burden on yourself?
憎まれ役まで
一人で請け負うつもりか！
So you plan on being the bad guy all by yourself too?
ｵﾚは知ってんだぞ！ ﾄｼ!!
I know how you feel, Toshi...
お前が ﾐﾂﾊﾞ殿を…》
...About Mitsuba-dono!
♪♪～
(蔵場)残念です…
ﾐﾂﾊﾞも悲しむでしょう｡
What a pity.
I'm sure Mitsuba will be sad, too.
古い友人を
亡くすことになるとは…｡
To lose one of her old friends.
あなたたちとは 仲よく
やっていきたかったのですよ｡
I really wanted to be on good terms with you people.
真選組の後ろ盾を得られれば
自由に商いができるというもの｡
If I got the backing of the Shinsengumi,
then I could run my business without any restrictions.
そのために 縁者に近づき
縁談まで設けたというのに…｡
That's why I approached one of your relatives and even set out to marry her,
まさか あのような病持ちとは…｡
but who knew she was that sick?
姉を握れば 総悟君は御しやすしと
踏んでおりましたが➡
I figured if I had his sister, then Sogo would be easy to control,
医者の話では
もう長くないとのこと｡
but according to her doctor, she doesn't have much time left to live.
非常に残念な話だ｡
It really is a pity.
ﾊﾅから ｵﾚたち抱き込むために➡
So from the start, you just used her to get us on your side?
ｱｲﾂを
利用するつもりだったのかよ｡
(蔵場)愛していましたよ！
I loved her.
商人は 利を生むものを
愛でるものです｡
As a merchant, I love things that will make me a profit.
ただし 道具としてですが…｡
But only as a tool.
あのような欠陥品に➡
She was damaged goods, but I gave her happiness like other people.
人並みの幸せを
与えてやったのです｡
感謝してほしいくらいですよ｡
If anything, she should thank me.
((せめてよ 死ぬ前に一時でも➡
I just want her to taste a bit of happiness like other people before she dies.
人並みの幸せ
味わわせてやりてえんですよ))
ﾍﾍｯ… 外道とは言わねえよ｡
It's not like you're that much of a nonconformist, you know.
ｵﾚも似たようなもんだ｡
You and I are alike.
ひでえこと 腐るほどやってきた｡
I've also done countless horrible acts.
あげく死にかけてるときに
その旦那 たたき斬ろうってんだ｡
And to top it off, I'm trying to kill the husband of a woman who's dying.
ひでえ話だ…｡
Yeah, that's pretty cruel.
同じ穴のﾑｼﾞﾅというやつですかな｡
So you can say, we're like two of a kind.
鬼の副長とは
よく言ったものです｡
No wonder they call you the demon Vice-Chief.
あなたとは気が合いそうだ…｡
I think you and I will get along well.
そんな大層なもんじゃねえよ！
That's really...
...an exaggeration.
♪♪～
ｵﾚは ただ…｡
I just...
惚れた女にゃ
幸せになってほしいだけだ！
...want the girl I love to be happy.
(土方)こんなところで 刀
振り回してるｵﾚにゃ ﾑﾘな話だが➡
A life like that is impossible for a guy like me who lives by the sword.
どっかで
普通の野郎と所帯もって➡
I just wanted her to marry a normal guy somewhere,
普通にｶﾞｷ産んで
普通に生きてってほしいだけだ｡
have kids like everyone else and live a normal life.
ただ そんだけだ…｡
That's all...
なるほど…
やはり お侍様の考えることは➡
I see...
Well, like I said, it's hard for us merchants to understand how a samurai thinks.
私たち下郎には
計りかねまするな｡
撃て～！
Fire!!
うぉ～っ！
(爆発音)
何事です？
(手下)わかりません｡
What's going on?
I-I don't know.
(近藤)いけ～！
Go!
(手下)し… 真選組だ～！
It's the Shinsengumi!
♪♪～
ﾄｼ～！
Toshi!!
(銃声)
(手下)死ね～！
Die!
(爆発音)
Toshi!!
(近藤)ﾄｼ～！
(蔵場)車を出しなさい｡
(手下)はい｡
Start the car.
Yes, sir.
とんだ誤算…｡
I misjudged them.
やはり野蛮な猿と
手を組もうなどと➡
I guess it's impossible to work with barbaric monkeys after all.
ﾑﾘな話でしたか…｡
病院へ 向かいなさい｡
Head to the hospital.
That woman may be dying but she can still be used as a hostage.
あの女 死にかけとはいえ
人質くらいには なるでしょう｡
ぐぁぁぁ～っ…!!
(蔵場)ｷ… ｷｻﾏ…！
You bastard!!
Sh-Shake him off!
(蔵場)ふ… 振り落とせ～！
何を やっている！
What the hell are you doing?
(蔵場)早く 撃ち殺せ～!!
Hurry up and shoot him!
うわ～っ！ あぁぁぁ～っ!!
ﾃﾒｴ…!?
You!
あぁぁぁ～っ!!
安心しな！
Don't worry.
せんべい 買いにきただけさ！
I just went to get some rice crackers for her.
You go deliver it to her!
ﾃﾒｴらで 届けてやりな！
そのほうが ｱｲﾂも喜ぶだろう｡
I'm sure she'll be happier to get them from you.
♪♪～
ぐおぉぉぉ～っ!!
うわぁぁぁ～っ!!
がぁぁぁぁ～っ!!
((ﾐﾂﾊﾞ:私を 置いていくんだもの｡
You're leaving me behind.
(ﾐﾂﾊﾞ)浮気なんて しちゃﾀﾞﾒよ｡
So make sure you don't go astray.
(ﾐﾂﾊﾞ)きっと
自分の道を 貫いてくださいね｡
Walk down the path you have chosen for yourself.
Please...okay...?
(ﾐﾂﾊﾞ)きっと… きっとよ…))
(爆発音)
♪♪～
(沖田)姉上… ごめんなさい…｡
Sis...
I'm sorry...
(沖田)ｵﾚは…
ろくでもねえ 弟だ…｡
I'm...a good-for-nothing brother.
結局…
姉上の幸せを 奪ってきたのは…➡
In the end, I'm the one who robbed you of your happiness.
ｵﾚ…｡ ごめんなさい…！
I'm sorry.
ごめん…｡
Sorry...
♪♪～
総ちゃん… いいの…｡
So-chan,
it's okay.
よく がんばったわね…｡
You've worked so hard...
You've grown...grown up into such a great man.
立派に… 立派になった…｡
本当に… 強くなった…｡
You've gotten so strong.
姉上… 強くなんか… ねえ…｡
...Sis.
I'm not strong... I'm not... I'm...
ﾎﾞｸは… ｵﾚは…｡
振り返っちゃ… ﾀﾞﾒ…｡
You mustn't look back...
(ﾐﾂﾊﾞ)決めたんでしょう…？
You're the one who decided, right? Back then...
(ﾐﾂﾊﾞ)自分で あのとき…｡
(ﾐﾂﾊﾞ)自分で 選んだ道でしょう？
It was the path you chose.
(ﾐﾂﾊﾞ)だったら…➡
Then you mustn't apologize...
謝ったりしたら ﾀﾞﾒ…｡
泣いたりしたら… ﾀﾞﾒ…｡
And you mustn't cry...
(ﾐﾂﾊﾞ)わき見もしないで
前だけ見て 歩いていく…｡
You never looked back.
You just looked straight ahead and kept walking.
I loved looking at your backs as you walked away.
(ﾐﾂﾊﾞ)あなたたちの背中を
見るのが 好きだった…｡
(ﾐﾂﾊﾞ)ぶっきらぼうで…➡
You were all gruff, impudent and clumsy.
ふてぶてしくって…
不器用で…｡
でも 優しい あなたたちが…➡
Yet you were all so kind and I loved you for that.
大好きだった…｡
だから… 私…➡
That's why... I...was so very happy.
とっても… 幸せだった…｡
To have been able to meet wonderful people like you.
あなたたちのように…
ｽﾃｷな人たちと 出会えて…｡
(ﾐﾂﾊﾞ)あなたみたいな…➡
To have had...a wonderful little brother like you...
ｽﾃｷな… 弟を もてて…｡
(ﾐﾂﾊﾞ)総ちゃん…➡
So-chan...
あなたは…➡
You are...
私の…➡
...the brother I am so proud of...
自慢の弟… よ…｡
♪♪～
[Super Spicy Rice Crackers]
(土方)かれえ…｡
Man, this is spicy.
So spicy!
かれえよ…｡
Dammit, what the hell...?
なんだ？ これ｡ ﾁｷｼｮｳ…｡
辛すぎて 涙が出てきやがった…｡
It's so spicy, it's making me cry...
かれえ…｡
Man, it's spicy...
It's spicy.
かれえ…｡
[Preview]
The brave warriors of Babel are trying to stop the construction of the Filthy Tower.
The next episode... "The Most Exciting Part of a Group Date is Before it Starts."
[The brave warriors of Babel are trying to stop the construction of the Filthy Tower.]
[Will they be able to stop the horrible plan?]